Guide to the Wilfred Healey Stone Papers SC0975
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2010-002
  - E. M. Forster and Bloomsbury Materials
    - Talk on EMF for Stanford Alumni Association, Feb. 1992 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - “Forster the Environmentalist” – typescript of article published in Seeing Double, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with Carola Kaplan about “Forster the Environmentalist” article, 1995-97 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Letter from Pamela Diamond (Roger Fry), 1977 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence re talks to local book clubs on Forster, 1989-93 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Files
    - South Africa and controversies over apartheid, with Stone’s letter to the Stanford Daily and correspondence with Bill Chace (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Materials on issues: “melting pot,” theme houses, and fraternities and sororities, including Stone’s letter to the Daily, 1990-94 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Early versions of “The Balloon Man” and correspondence re publication, 1956-98 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Restricted Files
    - Alden, Patricia Ann (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Armstrong, Paul B. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Bazin, Nancy (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Brattin, Joel (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Brown, Emerson (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Comstock, Craig (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Cusic, Carla (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Delapa, Michael Dominic (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Eckels, Jon (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Felstiner, John (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Foster, John (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Gelpi, Albert and Barbara (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Gerzina, Gretchen (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Hackling, Donald Chester (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Harris, Dale (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Harris, Elizabeth Hall (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Hessler, John (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Irvine, William (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Johnston, Judy (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Kelvin, Norman (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Klein, Eugene A. (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Kluwin, Tom (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Levin, Dave (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - L’Heureux, John (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Materer, Tim (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - McClure, John (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Mellor, Anne (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Packer, Nancy (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Pearkes, Timothy W. (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Peterson, Jan (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Polhemus, Rob (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Pratt, Branwen (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Rebholz, Ron (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Shell, Marc (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Williams, Margaret (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Weatherhead, Andrea (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Webb, Igor (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Wilson, Neville (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Wong, David T. K. (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Zaniello, Thomas (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Zaragozza, Nick (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Recommendation letters (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Recommendation letters (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Recommendation letters (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Ph.D. committee and exams (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - NEH. Forms with individual’s social security numbers (pulled from files in box 11) (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2013-054
  - Typescript re Tennyson (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Tennyson illustrations (slides) (Box 6, Folder 2)